hookedonhouses.net 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy & Disclosure - Hooked on Houses

1\. “Hooked on Houses” is a legally trademarked name.

2\. I _always_ strive to give credit for photo images that I use and link to the original source. If you find that one is attributed in error or if I have used one of yours and you want it removed, [let me know](https://hookedonhouses.net/contact-julia/).

3\. This site uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

4\. This is a personal blog written and edited by [Julia Sweeten](https://hookedonhouses.net/about-2/). It accepts advertising and other forms of compensation. I rarely run sponsored posts or use affiliate links, but when I do, I state so clearly. I always give my honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely my own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

5. Hooked on Houses is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

6\. Re: GDPR Compliance, the privacy of my visitors is important to me. I never sell or share your personal information with anyone else. When you leave a comment and include your e-mail address or sign up for my weekly newsletter, it is never seen by anyone but me.

7\. When visiting this site, your personal data may be collected. In some cases we need to collect and store personal data in order to provide services or information that you request from us (ex: newsletters). We collect information regarding your website behavior, communication, and interaction with this site. This information may be connected to existing personal data that has been stored for a specified and defined purpose.

8\. We obtain personal data when you visit our site and accept cookies; submit a contact form; send an email; or sign up for newsletters. I never add anyone to my mailing list unless they have requested I do so by filling out one of my [subscription forms](https://www.subscribepage.com/hookedonhouses). It is never sold or shared with anyone else.

9\. This site uses tracking and scripts from third parties that collect information about how visitors use it. This way we can see where our web traffic is coming from and which pages are getting the most views. We use this information to further improve and develop the content of our website and our digital advertising.

10. Hooked on Houses uses MailerLite to manage our email marketing subscriber list and to send emails to our subscribers. MailerLite is a third-party provider, which may collect and process your data using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our newsletter. You can read MailerLite’s privacy policy [here](https://www.mailerlite.com/privacy-policy). You can always unsubscribe from the Hooked on Houses newsletter by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided at the end of each newsletter.

11\. By visiting this site and submitting your personal information for comments and newsletters, you accept that your personal data will be processed according to this privacy policy.

#### Full Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: https://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

#### For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

(Visited 385 times, 1 visits today)
